

Marco Chavez

(559) 682-2888 Unsettlesea@gmail.com Fresno, CA

Professional Summary

Soon to be graduate of Woz U specializing in JavaScript development with a 3.0. Strong innovated professional with Node.js a passion for Full Stack Web Development and Software Development. Practicing Software Development for 2 years and continuing my technical education in order to become an integral part of a Software Development team.

Work History

BouMatic - Quality Control Chemical Tech

Fresno, California

08/2018 - Current

- Mastered an inventory management GUI to query and send information to databases to keep our inventory accurate, while using lab equipment to get results from chemicals to make sure they are in specification.
- Administered functions in Excel to display complex data and organize it into a more readable format.
- Helped oversee operations by making sure we started on the correct orders first.

Future Ford of Clovis - Internet Sales Representative

07/17 - 10/17

- Evaluated a customer database that was constantly being updated by online requests, and give those customers calls and emails.
- Maintained that the customers were being responded to shortly after they were added to our database.
- Dressed appropriately in order to give customers a professional experience.

T-Mobile - Mobile Expert

Fresno, California

10/2017 - 04/2018

- Surveyed customer's accounts when they needed anything changed and break down what data usage meant on our network.
- Quickly use math in order to calculate what a new customers' bills would be.

Skills

- Software development
- Web development
- Programming
- API design knowledge
- Software testing
- JavaScript specialist
- Operating Systems
- NodeJs
- Angular
- React
- SQL, MySQL, MongoDB, NoSQL
- ExpressJS
- HTML, CSS
- TypeScript
- MVC (Model, View, Controller)
- Amazon Web Services
- Version Control
- jQuery
- Bootstrap, Foundation
- ReduxJS
- C programming language
- Python
- Heroku
- Communication skills
- Interpersonal skills
- Inventory management
- Excel
- Purchasing
- Retail
- Management
- Time management

Education

2019

Woz U - Education. Reprogrammed. Software Developement

• Projected a good image, by dressing professionally.

Lithia Motors, Inc - Product Specialist

11/2016 - 04/2017

- Facilitated my network of customers through a customer retail management system.
- Explained to customers how financing works, which meant being as accurate as possible with my math, and with my communication skills.

Alorica - Agent

07/2016 - 11/2016

- Mediated customers' accounts.
- Pioneered strong interpersonal skills to de-escalate situations where customers became upset and learned how to get to the real issues that the customers were having.
- Explained what data utilization meant for customers who were not on unlimited data plans.
- Performed in a very confidential environment.

Information Technology

2015

Fresno High High school diploma